-TIME IS BREAKING DOWN.
MONARCH HAS BEEN PREPARING FOR IT.
THERE'S THIS THING.
IT'S CALLED THE LIFEBOAT PROTOCOL, AND IT CAN SAVE US -- AT LEAST SOME OF US.
-YOU'VE BEEN THE FACE OF MONARCH FOR ALL THESE YEARS, MARTIN, BUT LET'S GET CLEAR ON SOMETHING.
THIS IS STILL MY SHIP.
-YOU'RE NOT THINKING CLEARLY. YOU NEED YOUR TREATMENT.
-YOU GONNA GO?
-ME? GO TO A PARTY?
-WE CAN ROLL TOGETHER IF YOU WANT.
-WHAT DO YOU WANT?
-ANYONE WHO MIGHT IMPLICATE MONARCH.
-FUCK YOU.
-HMM.
-WAIT! [ GUNSHOT ]
-WE JUST LOST COMMUNICATION WITH JACK JOYCE'S TRANSPO'.
FIND HIM.
-STEP AWAY! RIGHT NOW!
-LIAM, THIS ISN'T WHAT IT LOOKS LIKE.
NO. NO!
HE'S GONE.
-WE NEED ALL POINTS CONVERGED ON LIAM BURKE.
HE'S ARMED AND DANGEROUS.
[ INDISTINCT SHOUTING ]