-PAUL SERENE'S BECOME UNHINGED.
-WHAT ABOUT MY TREATMENTS?
-HE'S TRIGGERED A CATASTROPHE.
-THE JOYCE FIELD COULD COLLAPSE WITHIN EIGHT HOURS.
-HE HAS THE CHANCE TO FIX IT, BUT HE'S CHOOSING NOT TO.
HE'S CHOOSING TO LET THINGS END.
AND THIS IS WHERE WE COME IN.
[ BEEP ]
-GOOD EVENING, DR. AMARAL.
-WE'RE FIVE MINUTES OUT, MR. HATCH.
-I'VE COME TO FREE YOU, MY FRIEND.
IT'S TIME FOR YOU TO REJOIN THE OTHERS, TO RETURN TO THE INFINITE.
WHAT WAS TROUBLING ME IS WHO GOT THEM INTO KIM'S LAB.
SHE PAID A VISIT MINUTES BEFORE THE EXPLOSION.
-SOFIA'S LOYAL.
IF THE FRACTURE'S HAPPENING NOW, I OWE THIS TO HER.
[ KNOCK ON DOOR ]
-DR. HOLDEN. THE PROTOCOL'S BEEN INITIATED.
-LIAM?
-[ YELLS ]
[ CELLPHONE RINGS ]
-YEAH?
-SIR, I HAVE SOME INFORMATION ABOUT MARTIN HATCH.
-I WANT HIM APPREHENDED, IMMEDIATELY.